Christopher Yates Papers
Christopher Yates Papers
- Restricted material
  - Originals of items listed above as restricted (Box 6)
Sickels, Thomas 1778 Oct 2 Albany 1779 Feb 23 Albany 1779 Mar 11 Albany 1779 Mar 27 Albany 1779 Apr 9 Albany 1779 Apr 21 Albany 1779 May 5 Albany 1779 May 13 Albany 1779 May 15 Albany 1779 May 19 Albany 1779 Jun 15 Albany 1779 Jul 26 Albany 1779 Aug 4 Albany 1779 Sep 7 Albany 1779 Sep 29 Albany 1779 Oct 22 Albany 1780 Feb 16 Albany 1780 Apr 26 Albany 1780 Aug 21 Albany 1778 Aug 20 Albany
Sivart[?], Dirck 1779 Oct 22 Stillwater
Smith, S.P. 1832 Oct 22 Charleston to Elizabeth (DeLancey) Yates 1835 Jul 8 New York City to Elizabeth (DeLancey) Yates
Stark, Ca. 1778 Jun 16 Albany
Stockwell, Levi 1779 Sep 3 Skenesborough
Street, Raymond B. 1776 May 6 Skenesborough 1776 Jul 29 Skenesborough 1776 Aug Skenesborough 1776 Aug Skenesborough 1776 Aug 2 Skenesborough
Tapp, William 1779 Apr 21 Fort George
Taylor, John 1776 Oct 16 Skenesborough 1776 Oct 18 Ticonderoga
Ten Brouk, Peter 1773 Mar 17 at his house to "Sir"
Tillman, John 1779 Mar 3 Continental Shoe factory, Albany 1779 Mar 15 Continental Shoe factory, Albany 1779 Sep 22 Albany
Toleman, Thomas 1780 May 12 Fort Edward
Truax, Isaac 1758 May 22 Schenectady to Peter Van Benthuysen 1758 Nov 18 Schenectady to Peter Van Benthuysen
Tyson, — 1781 May 25 Fishkill 1781 Dec 22 Fishkill
Van Benthuysen, Peter 1761 Dec 17 New York City to Peter Van Benthuysen, Sr. 1761 Aug 7 New York City to Peter Van Benthuysen, Sr. 1761 Sep 12 New York City to Peter Van Benthuysen, Sr. c. 1761 Dec 31 New York City to Peter Van Benthuysen, Sr. 1762 Oct 14 New York City to Peter Van Benthuysen, Sr.
Van Ingen, Dick 1783 Jan 19 Schenectady
Van J--, W. 1798 Charleston to M. Van [Avery]
Van Vechten, Jennis 1778 Jun 24 Albany 1779 Aug 17 Albany 1780 May 11 Albany 1780 May 19 Albany
Van Veighton 1777 Mar 15 Saratoga 1780 May 2 Albany
Vernor, John 1781 Jan 29 Saratoga to Nicholas Quackenbush 1781 Feb 5 Saratoga to Nicholas Quackenbush 1781 May 16 Saratoga 1784 Feb 7 Saratoga
Wagener, T. 1779 Jun 18 1779 Jun 21 1779 Jun 26 1779 Jul 7 Canajoharie 1779 Jul 24 Lake Otsego
Washington, George 1778 Jun 29 near Monmouth Court House to Gen. Gates (copy)
Waterbury, David 1776 Aug 31 Skenesborough undated
Waters, Anthony 1768 Jul 16 Fort Stanwix to Joseph Yates
Watkins, Anna c. 1835 Mar 11 Lexington, Ga. to Elizabeth (DeLancey) Yates
Watkins, J.W.D. 1834 Apr 11 New York City to Joseph C. Yates
Watkins, W.D. & Anna 1824 Jun 29 Thomville to Elizabeth (DeLancey) Yates
Wemp[?], A. 1779 Mar 7 Schenectady
Wendell, W. 1776 Aug 18 Skenesborough 1776 Aug 27 Skenesborough
Wilkie, Jacob 1775 Sep 6 New Lebanon
Wilkie, William 1776 Aug 13 Schenectady 1776 Aug 20 Schenectady
Willett, N. 1783 May 6 to Capt. [Boaf]
Windell, Jacob 1776 Jun 19 Stillwater
Wynkoop, Cornelius 1776 Oct 17 Skenesborough 1776 Oct 25 Skenesborough 1776 Nov 19 Skenesborough 1776 Dec 5 Skenesborough
Yates, Ann 1846 Apr 28 Schenectady to Elizabeth (DeLancey) Yates
Yates, Christopher [undated], to unknown [undated], to Gerret Visscher 1776 Jan 5 Schenectady to Walter Livingston 1776 Apr 3 Palatine 1776 Nov 25 Fort Gates to Col. Wynkoop 1777 Apr 7 Fort Ann to Committee (of Safety), Kingsburg district 1777 Apr 23 Fort Ann to Col. Hay 1777 Apr 23 Fort Ann to Ph. Lansing 1777 May 4 to Col. Hay 1779 Jan 9 Saratoga to Morgan Lewis 1779 Feb 4 Saratoga to Morgan Lewis 1779 Mar 23 Saratoga to Palmer 1779 Apr 20 Saratoga, to unknown 1779 May 12 to Thomas Sickels 1779 Jun 30 Camp at Canajoharie to Com— at Albany 1779 Dec 29 Saratoga to Abraham Yates 1780 Apr 10 to Thomas Sickels 1780 May 10 Saratoga to Morgan Lewis 1780 May 16 to Jennis Van Veighton 1780 May 17 to Jennis Van Veighton 1780 May 29 Fort Edward to Joseph Peak 1780 Jul 15 Saratoga to Morgan Lewis 1780 Sep 4 Schenectady to Morgan Lewis 1780 Oct 30 Saratoga to Morgan Lewis 1780 Nov 26 Stillwater to Hugh Hughes 1781 Feb 12 Saratoga to Maj. Quackenbush 1781 Apr 11 Saratoga to Maj. Quackenbush 1781 Apr 11 Saratoga to Maj. Quackenbush 1781 Apr 12 Saratoga to Maj. Quackenbush 1781 Apr 13 Saratoga to Maj. Quackenbush 1781 Apr 16 Saratoga to Maj. Quackenbush 1781 Jul 14 Saratoga, to unknown 1781 Aug 22 Saratoga to Maj. Quackenbush 1781 Sep 5 Saratoga, to unknown 1781 Sep 8 Saratoga, to unknown 1781 Sep 12 Saratoga to Oliver Glean 1781 Sep 14 Saratoga to Oliver Glean 1781 Dec 20 Saratoga, to unknown 1782 Feb 21 Schenectady to Hugh Hughes 1784 Jul 8, to unknown
Yates, John A. c. 1845 to Elizabeth (DeLancey) Yates
Yates, William 1767 Nov 18 Albany 1778 Jul 2 Albany
Young, George H. 1834 Feb 17 Lexington, Ga. to Elizabeth (De Lancey) Yates
Younglove, John 1776 Nov 15 Cambridge 1776 Nov 15 Cambridge to Lt. Jenner Palmer